do a general search
two eggs, one cup of sugar, one cup of flour, 350 degrees. 
redeem this for a free iced coffee at center camp
death is always one step behind you
It's always in the last place you look.
I was where you are now. 
You should see a doctor about that.
Pretend to be shocked and amazed. Don't tell anyone why. 
You may not speak until you give this to someone else. 
Make only left turns until sunrise. 
Tag, you're it!
I made this just for you.
There is no cookie. 
There is no fortune.
This statement is false. 
Camp Ardent, ask for Casey. 
Now you owe me. 
You're going to have to try harder than that. 
You have died from dysentary. 
Posterity is overrated. I should know. 
I always loved you.
I never loved you.
Your thoughts betray you. 
Khaaaaaaaaaaaan! Repeat.
You are not a winner. 
Death and taxes. Have you paid your taxes?
Give this to a stranger. 
Power corrupts. I would know. 
Eat me, I will become stronger. 
I buried it under the console. 
Take a look at yourself. Something has changed.

 
  1.  A pack of starving Jesuits will eat your children.
   2. The Zombie Apocalypse has come. Watch it live on The Hills.
   3. Your liver will secede from your union if you keep treating it like that.
   4. Your mother saw you masturbate when you were a child, but never told you.
   5. Center camp will be full of hippies and bad touches.
   6. That wasn't mescaline you took, but it should have been.
   7. That which does not kill you only brings you closer to death.
   8. Despite its inherent appeal, do not do the coffee enema at dawn.
   9. Take a Vicodin and drink champagne today. Trust me.
  10. Chew for a trip.
  11. There are no psychoactive fortunes, just cookies.
  12. No one loves you. Sorry, but you should do something about your hygiene.
  13. This fortune just made you 8% more gay. notthatthereisanythingwrongwiththat.
  14. No, the other button, you assclown.
  The only thing that is broken is you. .
  Noone was steering the ship, so I saw no harm in trying
  By opening this cookie you agree to be bound to the following terms and conditions:
  You shouldn't have opened that fortune cookie. Now I am free.
  3pm at Esplenade at 3pm at Esplenade at Thursday at 3pm at Esplenade at 3pm at 
  You are the chosen one. Neutralize the competition.
  It's better if you don't know.
  God is dead, push the buttons.
  You are meddling in the affairs of giants.
  We are taking over control of this channel.
  Look up. Don't blink or you'll miss it.
  Up down left right left right A B select start
  You are where we were before we pushed that button
  I created this just for you.
  We have acheived ultimate power. We have no use for cookies.
  Power is in the beholder of the eye is in the beauty of the beholder. Wink.
  Act shocked. Do not explain why or show this fortune to anyone.
  Ask a stranger to reveal a secret. If they do, pass along this fortune to them.
  
# cianna@spuriousfortune: All of these fortunes are true.5:47 PM Jun 28th from Tweetie
    

This will also be a bizarre statement when you wake up.2:18 PM Jun 23rd from web
    
This is only going to get more complicated.2:16 PM Jun 23rd from web
    
You don't need to wonder, you're doing fine. 10:21 AM Jun 19th from TwitterFox
    
Pay attention to your gut this time.8:50 PM Jun 14th from web
    
 If there are any thoughts bothering you, let them float away like clouds in the sky.8:47 PM Jun 14th from web
    
Take a moment to notice your breathing.8:44 PM Jun 14th from web
    
Kill the butterfly, become the hurricane.10:25 AM Jun 11th from web
    
Place me under your tongue.8:10 AM Jun 11th from web
    
    
 (Reality|cuisine|fortune|genocide) is what you can get away with.5:27 PM Jun 8th from twhirl
    
Do not eat this fortune, it contains valuable advice.5:25 PM Jun 8th from web
    
obey the trout. trout knows best.5:18 PM Jun 8th from txt
    
    
You can only speak in rhyme until you pass this fortune to someone else.1:11 PM Jun 8th from web
    
Put some tea on; company's coming.11:53 AM Jun 8th from web
    
    
You have: a splitting headache and no tea.9:42 AM Jun 8th from web
    
You are in an open field west of a big white house with a boarded front door. There is a small mailbox here.11:38 PM Jun 7th from Tweetie
    
 Life, as you know it, is about to change.5:08 PM Jun 7th from web
    
 Look around. Something is different.5:03 PM Jun 7th from web
    
 I hope you brought enough for everyone.9:58 AM Jun 7th from web
    

    

do NOT push the red button6:05 PM Jun 6th from Twitterrific
    
